

Address Phoenix Arizona, United States

Contact 1 970 541 0135 benbarker0311@gmail.com

Date of Birth January 20, 1994

PROFILE

Over 8 years of extensive development experience, By using Node JS, ReactJS and JavaScript MVC frameworks such as Angular and BackboneJS for designing UI applications and distributed application architecture, object-oriented design, and web based applications. Experience in developing blockchain web application using web3.js such as Solana and Ethereum.

EDUCATION

April 2011 - August 2014

Nagoya Institute of Technology, Nagoya, Japan B.S. in Computer Science

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

PHP

NodeJS HTML5 & CSS3

Javascript & TypeScript

ReactIS

Angular

SQL & NoSQL

***** ***** ***** ****

SKILLS

- ✓ NextJS, Redux, Material UI, Storybook and UI Toolkit
- ✓ Restful API, Cloud Service, GraphQL, SOAP, WebRTC
- ✓ AWS, Azure, Babel,Grunt, Webpack, Docker and Git
- ✓ Wordpress, Laravel, Ethereum, Solana and Web3.js
- ✓ MERN Stack, MEAN Stack and PERN Stack
- ✓ MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL and Firebase
- ✓ SEO, Nginx, Apache, Tomcat, TCP/IP, UDP, HTTP/2, TSL

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- https://yournfthub.com
- https://plasbit.com
- https://cropper.finance
- https://furrsols.io

• https://www.solanacash.io (Solana Staking Site)

(Solana Marketplace)
(With MeteorJS)
(Solana Launchpad)
(P2E site with MERN)
(Solana Staking Site)

KSAN ARAKI

Senior Front-end Engineer

www

http://ksanaraki.netlify.app

EXPERIENCE

September 2021 - July 2022

PlasBit Ltd, London, United Kingdom

Senior Front-end Engineer

- Developed of the company website by leading an Agile team of 5 developers
- Responsibilities in the Requirement Analysis,
 Design, Implementation, Testing and Maintenance.
- Developed by ReactJS, and MeteorJS which is a Full Stack Framework and based on the MVC pattern.
- Implemented new responsive, mobile-first approach which increased mobile traffic by 20%.
- Worked with Quality Assurance to get new pages/products tested, and addressed all issues.
- Rewrote HTML for SEO and Accessibility, for maintain, 600% increase in users in 3 months.

October 2017 - August 2021

KASUGAI Co.Ltd, Nagoya, Japan

Senior Front-end Engineer

- Responsibility in develop and maintain internal websites with doing Jenkins builds, configuring webpack or UI/unit testing frameworks.
- Replaced existed Angular JS code with Angular JS6.0 which is latest technology at that time, which built web apps which are more user interactive.
- Implemented AWS to allow easy iteration in company cloud infrastructure.
- Developed a new admin panel for purchasing agent business, which increased the service by 70% and improved operating efficiency by over 20%.
- Implemented CSS3, DOM Api, DOJO and Ajax to create a dynamic and interactive experience.
- Utilized MVC, Prototype and Singleton JS patterns to develop application Coded frontend interface with Bootstrap, AngularJS, CSS, JS and HTML5.

September 2014 - September 2017

Juroku Bank, Ltd, Nagoya, Japan

Senior Front-end Engineer

- Development of a well responsive single page application using AngularJS and JavaScript in conjunction with HTML5, CSS3 standards.
- Designed a new, user interactive landing page, utilizing tools like HTML5, XHTML, CSS3 and SCSS, achieving a 5.5/6 user score.
- Joined with web designers to develop user interfaces and prototypes for a web-based internal financial manager system.
- Boosted the conversion rate by 90% by improving the design.